sanus.com 2018-01-28

# Privacy Policy | SANUS

SANUS ("SANUS") recognizes and respects the privacy of our online visitors, so we provide you with this Privacy Policy to inform you of our online information practices and the choices available regarding the collection and use of your information. This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected off the www.sanus.com website. SANUS values the trust its customers place in the company. Accordingly, SANUS adheres to the highest ethical standards in gathering, using, and safeguarding customer information that is entrusted to the company.

### Website Visitors

Our web server automatically recognizes and stores the visitor's IP address (the Internet address of visitor's computer) of each visitor browsing our website to determine which areas of our site are being visited and the amount of time each visitor has spent there. This information helps us to understand visitors' traffic patterns through our website so that we can enhance the overall usability of our website. Your computer provides this information automatically each time you log on, unless you have activated blocking technology available in some browsers. While we do not generally require that you provide us with individually identifiable information in order to visit and use our website, at times we may ask you to provide us with personal information such as your E-mail address, name, mailing address, telephone number, credit card number, demographic information, or persistent identifier (such as user name and password), which is associated with individually identifiable information to enable you to make a purchase, register a product, correspond with SANUS, enter a sweepstakes, participate in an online survey, subscribe to a mailing list or newsletter, or register for special purchase discounts. If you choose not to provide an identifier for those activities, you may not be able to participate in them.

### Personal Information

The information you provide will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with SANUS. Among other things, SANUS wants to use this data to accommodate your experience on our website. Unless you instruct us otherwise, we will send you information about our various product upgrades, special offers, and other new products and services from SANUS that we feel may be of interest to you. Only SANUS (or agents working on behalf of SANUS and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings. If you do not want to receive such mailings, see the Opt-Out procedures below.

SANUS will not share your personal information with any outside organization for its use in marketing or solicitation without your consent. Your information may be shared with agents, contractors or distributors of SANUS for the purposes of selling our products or performing our services. For instance, if SANUS needs to ship something to you, they may share your name and address with a shipping company. SANUS provides third party agents with the minimum amount of information needed to complete the requested service or transaction.

SANUS protects the personal information you share with it. At SANUS, access to your personal information is limited to persons who need the information for completion of a requested service or transaction. In addition, it is SANUS's policy to maintain the integrity of any personal information within its possession. To prevent security breaches, SANUS collects and stores all personal information in a separate location from this website, with no connection to the Internet or any other network. You can make changes to your personal information by e-mailing your changes to [info@sanus.com](mailto:info@sanus.com).

### Juvenile Information

SANUS will NOT knowingly collect online contact information from children under the age of 13. If SANUS learns that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems.

### Linked Websites

Other sites which are linked to or from our website (including the websites of affiliates) may have different policies. Since we do not control these websites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on those sites for details.

### Opt-Out Procedures

You may, at any moment, opt-out of our use of your personal information. To do so, please e-mail us at info@sanus.com. The staff at SANUS will remove your personal information from our database(s) as soon as reasonably possible.

### Policy Governs Use; Changes to Privacy Policy

The terms of this policy will govern the use and any information collected while it is in place. SANUS reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Changes to this privacy policy are effective at the time they are posted to this site.

**Last update: 11/6/2003.**

### Questions

For any questions or comments regarding SANUS' Privacy Policy or website, please contact us.
